let array = [
    {
        "question": "How many Major Languages?",
        "answer": "3",
        "color": "bg-red-500"
    },

    {
        "question": "Capital of the country?",
        "answer": "Abuja",
        "color": "bg-gray-500"
    },

    {
        "question": "Weather patterns",
        "answer": "2",
        "color": "bg-green-500"
    },

    {
        "question": "Current president",
        "answer": "Buhari",
        "color": "bg-lime-500"
    },

    {
        "question": "Richest Man",
        "answer": "Dangote",
        "color": "bg-teal-500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Popular Foods",
        "answer": "Jollof Rice",
        "color": "bg-sky-500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Closet Neighbors",
        "answer": "Ghana, Cotonou",
        "color": "bg-yellow-500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Most popular sport",
        "answer": "Soccer",
        "color": "bg-purple-500"
    },    
    {
        "question": "Currency",
        "answer": "Naira",
        "color": "bg-blue-500"
    },    
    {
        "question": "Most spoken Language",
        "answer": "Pidgin",
        "color": "bg-orange-500"
    },

    
]
export default array